[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110904pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WP", "NN", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "MD", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 3, "question": "Is Jon Huntsman the real deal?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 4, "answer": "I was the only candidate who stood up on the debt ceiling debate and said this country shouldn't default.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jon Huntsman"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["United States"]}, "docId": "110904pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "."], "qSentId": 31, "question": "What is the Jon Huntsman vision for America?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 32, "answer": "Pre-eminence for the United States.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jon Huntsman"], "LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110904pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNP", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 42, "question": "Or should the American dream be slightly re- invented for the modern world?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "MD", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "VB", "RB", "-NONE-", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 43, "answer": "The American dream is the same.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["China", "China", "America"]}, "docId": "110904pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "TO", "NNP", "TO", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", ",", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", ",", "RB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 56, "question": "Why try to build something like they did the last generation?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 57, "answer": "You worked in China for a couple of years and you well know that when you compare bureaucracy to China to bureaucracy in America, one of the reasons that they are marching on, good or bad, whatever your view of it, is they are not consumed with red tape over every tiny thing they do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["China"]}, "docId": "110904pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "VBN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 59, "question": "But does America have a fundamental problem business wise with the sheer volume of paperwork, red tape; legalese stuff that I believe slows down modern business?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "NNP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBD", "NN", ":", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 60, "answer": "In an autocratic system like China, there's plenty of red tape.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110904pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 84, "question": "What values did he instill in you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NNS", "VBD", "PRP", "MD", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 85, "answer": "Hard work.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110904pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "CD", ",", "DT", "JJ", "CD", ",", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 98, "question": "What was the name of your band?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 99, "answer": "We had a lot of bands but the last one, the good one, was wizard.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Marie"]}, "docId": "110904pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "CC", "NNP", "VBD", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 112, "question": "Did you see potential conflict arising?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 113, "answer": "Donny and Marie did OK.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Beefheart"]}, "docId": "110904pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 116, "question": "Now is that true?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 117, "answer": "If you can tell me anything about Captain Beefheart, I'll give you an answer.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110904pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 139, "question": "Do you want to get your hand dirty in the grubbiness of running for high office and all that comes with it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "DT", "DT", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 140, "answer": "We've come this far.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110904pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 154, "question": "Are you comfortable that they're ready?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 155, "answer": "They have been raised in a public environment.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110904pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 163, "question": "Why is that and how do you change that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "IN", "CC", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 164, "answer": "Well, its early days.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["August"]}, "docId": "110904pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 168, "question": "When is the point when we should look at how you're performing and properly judge it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "CC", "RB", "NN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 169, "answer": "Not August.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110904pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 181, "question": "You really want to get me in trouble, do you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 182, "answer": "I do, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110904pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "RB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "JJS", "NNS", ",", "IN", "RB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 199, "question": "What is something that you would say to a friend over dinner?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 200, "answer": "I don't - well, I'll tell you what I told most people, if not everybody.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110904pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "CC", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 226, "question": "Do you have sympathy for him in the position he found himself in where he had such an intransigent part of the Republican Party really just refusing to compromise?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 227, "answer": "He appointed me and I stood up and took the appointment to serve my country.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110904pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 244, "question": "Where would you disagree with her?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 245, "answer": "Well, on the debt ceiling.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110904pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 254, "question": "On gay marriage?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 255, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110904pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 262, "question": "What is your view of abortion?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 263, "answer": "I am pro life.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110904pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ",", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 270, "question": "Do you think there are any other circumstances where you would think an abortion is acceptable?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 271, "answer": "Rape, incest and life of the mother would be the exceptions that I could live with.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110904pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", ":", "DT", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 272, "question": "When you see again intransigents by some of the particularly the tea party and of the Republican Party on this kind of thing, do you think again that it's bordering on bigotry?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 273, "answer": "ON HUNTSMAN: All I have to say I don't have a lot of patience on a lot of the non-economic issues.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110904pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 282, "question": "Would you endorse what he said?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 283, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110904pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 298, "question": "Do you like him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 299, "answer": "You know I don't know him that well.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110904pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "RP", "DT", "NNS", ",", "RB", "VBG", "RP", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 309, "question": "I mean you've said it in a very nice way but what you're basically doing is knifing him straight in the back, aren't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "VBZ", "VBG", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 310, "answer": "I'm just pointing out the facts, just pointing out the facts.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110904pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", ":"], "qSentId": 332, "question": "What about to a tea party candidate?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 333, "answer": "You know, anyone who's going -", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110904pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 336, "question": "Could you entertain such idea?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 337, "answer": "Captain Beefheart music, I assume you are talking about.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110904pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 356, "question": "You wouldn't rule out Michele Bachmann?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 357, "answer": "I'm not going to play the name game at all.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michele Bachmann"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["United States"]}, "docId": "110904pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "CC", "IN", "DT", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "."], "qSentId": 394, "question": "What the hell have you just said to me?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 395, "answer": "I said whatever I say you'll have no idea what it is and after that I said, my name in Chinese and I said I'm going to become the next president of the United States.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["21st century"]}, "docId": "110904pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 410, "question": "What is your view?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 411, "answer": "It's the most important relationship of the 21st century.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110904pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 425, "question": "Because it allows them to apply a pressure that may not be good for America?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "MD", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 426, "answer": "Of course it is unhealthy.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110904pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 435, "question": "Has the time come for America to simply pull out all of its troops now from Iraq and Afghanistan and just start on concentrating on domestic issues?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "TO", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "CC", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 436, "answer": "We have no choice, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America", "Iraq", "Afghanistan"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110904pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 450, "question": "Is it acceptable for America and its national psyche and morale to pull out of two countries where a war has not been won?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "NN", "TO", "VB", "RP", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 451, "answer": "It is a counter terror effort that we are waging.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110904pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 455, "question": "Are you redefining the nature of the conflict?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 456, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "110904pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 463, "question": "Are you more in the revenge business then?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 464, "answer": "No, I'm in the keep America safe business.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110904pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "TO", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "NN", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", "RB", "CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 479, "question": "If come this time next year the battle for the White House is you against Barack Obama, a man who believes he's your dear, dear friend, are you prepared to gun him down politically?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 480, "answer": "We'll have a good debate and it will be around the issues and it will be a complete, complete approach that speaks to economic expansion and job creation where he has failed the American people miserably and where we're going to bring our strength from our background.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["White House"], "PERSON": ["Barack Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110904pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "WDT", ":"], "qSentId": 482, "question": "Are you politically ruthless?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 483, "answer": "I've got what it takes to win and I've got the vision which -", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110904pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 485, "question": "Can you be ruthless?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 486, "answer": "Listen.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110904pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 490, "question": "Are you brutal at them?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 491, "answer": "of course I do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110904pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 522, "question": "When did you first meet John?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 523, "answer": "Careful.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110904pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 530, "question": "It must have been disappointing, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 531, "answer": "Oh, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110904pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "NN"], "qSentId": 536, "question": "You ride Harleys?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 537, "answer": "40-year rider", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110904pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 541, "question": "Is that right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 542, "answer": "Something like that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110904pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "EX", "."], "qSentId": 543, "question": "Why should he be president?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 544, "answer": "Because I think he's the greatest leader out there.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Utah"]}, "docId": "110904pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", ",", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 549, "question": "What is your great master plan?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 550, "answer": "The principles are the same, whether in Utah or whether on a national basis.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110904pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 569, "question": "Why would you vote against them?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 570, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110904pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBZ", "EX", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "RBR", "IN", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 576, "question": "What was the thinking there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 577, "answer": "The think is there that we had a little more love to give.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110904pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 583, "question": "Are you prepared for that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 584, "answer": "I don't know that you are ever prepared.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110904pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 599, "question": "Where do you see the line drawn in terms of your adherence to the Mormon faith?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "VBN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 600, "answer": "I have a deep belief in God.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110904pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "VBP", "CD", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 608, "question": "What would you say to that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 609, "answer": "Well, I'd say there are 13 million Mormons around the world today.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110904pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 624, "question": "Are you ready for this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 625, "answer": "I think so.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110904pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "WP", "RB", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 639, "question": "Now, are you the only member of your family that can do this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "MD", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 640, "answer": "You know, it just so happens that I have a daughter who actually plays somewhat.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110904pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 652, "question": "What are you going to play?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 653, "answer": "Don't embarrass me too bad.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110904pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 662, "question": "Are we agreed?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 663, "answer": "I have a coin you can flip if you want.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]